Merciful God give strength to my heart.
Give me energy to keep going.
Put in my mouth the words to talk clearly.
Make my voice powerful.
Merciful God give strength to my heart.
Give me energy to keep going.
Put in my mouth the words to talk clearly.
Make my voice powerful.
Merciful God give strength to my heart.
Put in my mouth the words to talk clearly.
Put in my mouth the words to talk clearly
Make my voice powerful.
Merciful God give strength to my heart.
Give me energy to keep going.
Put in my mouth the words to talk clearly.
Make my voice powerful
Merciful God give strength to my heart.
Give me more energy to keep going.
First, the people sleeping outside.
The ones who don't sleep here.
Bye, see you later.
But the others after, okay?
No! If you don't sleep here, you don't eat.
The ones who sleep here, will eat
Those who sleep here.
The ones from there, and there.
No, the people inside won't eat here.
No, no, no!
The people sleeping outside will be first.
No zig zag!
I was cutting his hair before, look at him now.
When I was shaving him, okay, but now what?
5178HJK
Get off.
Calm down, please.
This is so embarrassing, man.
This is so embarrassing, so embarrassing.
What's there to eat?
Nothing.
Calm down.
Look, if there's no queue...
If there's no queue, there's no food.
No food.
Queue up. Why don't you queue up?
No, no, no, no...
Let me out.
No, queue.
One queue, one queue.
There's enough for everyone
but please, please, calm down.
Calm down, please. Calm down, please.
WEST
How long have you been here in the Canaries?
Five months, first in Las Palmas and then here.
A month and fifteen days.
Here?
A month and a half.
Are you in the centre or are you here?
Both, I'm in both.
In both.
But you sleep in the centre, right?
Yes, sometimes.
Sometimes, because the weather's always changing.
You're staying at the centre, right
Do you have the ID card?
Yeah yeah, everyone here has the card.
There's people who've lost their place
at the centre, right?
Do you think the food's shit here, too?
Yeah the food's no good here, it's a shame,
but we're not here for that.
We're here to find a solution in order to work.
We're not here...
to eat and that, you know?
We're not here to stay in the Canaries.
There's people who go to the mainland, another country,
Italy, Germany, I don't know
It's just a period of your life.
Being here?
Yes, everyone's situation here is the same.
The whole situation of migrating is like this.
So you think that this whole situation is a phase in life?
And that you must have patience.
Yes, that's my opinion. You know?
Yeah, it's interesting.
I didn't come here to - hey ACCEM! feed me!
Not to eat.
You eat well in Morocco.
In Morocco you eat well, right?
Yes.
Yeah, you didn't come here for the food.
Exactly, exactly.
I want a solution.
A real solution.
Not just for me, but for everyone who's here.
Well Moustapha... A pleasure.
Thanks.
I'm going home to write tomorrow's article.
A pleasure.
All mine.
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
Okay.
Every day. Morning, afternoon, night. Every day.
Ten seconds, yes?
Up, next.
This... needle, okay?
Here... one, a little bit.
Two, a little bit more...
harder, harder, harder, harder...
Okay?
Were you taking anything for the pain?
Say it was about 20 days ago they gave me that cream.
They gave me that cream and I put it on,
and it did nothing, it's still the same.
He says that for four days.
Yes. Cream good?
Not good.
Sammi, are you ACCEM?
Why?
No, no, not good.
Yeah but the doctor has to see you.
I went to the clinic, already.
Some have told me they showed them the note,
and they've torn it up in their face.
We'll have to make him another one.
Rocio is going to put down "problem hand"
And you talk to the ACCEM doctor tomorrow, yes?
With the note.
Thank you very much.
Bye Sammi.
When you lift it... How is it?
It hurts more like that.
This way?
This way is okay.
This way... no, no. That's not okay.
Like this it hurts. Very bad.
Hello.
Hello, how's it going?
Everything okay?
Good, good.
Any news?
Up until now, nothing.
Oh?
There's nothing?
Still no appointment for the paper, or anything?
You're just waiting here. No paper or anything.
Nothing.
Nothing, just eating and sleeping.
You don't know what's coming.
I don't know anything.
Yeah, it's true.
What do you do with the money?
My family sends me money, but they're tired.
Any you call them and say, send me money?
Sell whatever you can,
sell the cows, the house, the car...
whatever to get money and be able to live here.
I've spent 4,000 euros so far.
What did we come here for?
For us to send them money, or the other way around?
Us to them, but only they send it to us.
I thought you were a rich kid from Brufut.
Look at me, I came without knowing any Spanish.
I'm not a rich kid.
But, why are we talking here?
You don't look good, what's wrong?
We're like family. We have to help each other,
look at me, I'm alone, you know English,
you're smart, you know how to write,
you'll have to help me.
I don't talk, I don't tend to talk to anyone,
but don't worry, if you need me to I'll help you.
What's up with you boy?
I've been thinking for days abou
our life here, and how hard it is.
Don't say that! Don't say that!
Everything happening is because God wants it so.
Thank God we're on Spanish soil.
Anyway, the Spanish government isn't
going to leave us on the streets.
You understand?
We're here, we have breakfast, lunch, dinner..
But the journey is very hard.
The journey is hard.
We were in the middle of the ocean for ten days.
More than ten days.
There were three or four days,
we were in the middle of the ocean
without food or water.
Some people started to vomit, others to die.
And we...
were saved by God.
If it wasn't for Him... We'd all be dead.
You'd be dead.
Yes, many people died.
I swear to God, you're not dead.
That's why you're here with me. You're not dead.
I told you it was four days with no food or water.
Four days without eating or drinking?
I vomited on the person next to me for four days.
How many people died in your dinghy?
More than ten people.
Oh my God!
I vomited on someone. I couldn't help it;
there were so many people on the dinghy.
This is the path chosen for us.
Sat here, think of what we've
been through to get here.
If you think on the hardship
of the journey, you'll go mad!
You'd go mad, boy. Trust me.
The truth hurts.
When you decide to emigrate,
you leave your parents behind,
your wife, kids, your family.
You make the decision of getting on
the dinghy, missing your people.
We all know what the sea is like,
how brutal the waves are.
It's very dangerous.
I know life isn't easy and that you have to fight,
but not everything needs to be difficult,
there also need to be good times.
You're terrible!
No, no no, close the circle.
We need to close it to play better.
Stop!
Hey! That's a foul!
Omar, Did you see? That's a foul!
Who fouled? I didn't even touch you.
Are we playing like men, or what?
You pushed him.
I pushed him inwards.
I pushed him cause he saw what I was going to do.
Good shoes, good price, not expensive.
43.
43, they're no good.
What's your size?
No, 40. No, they're too.... 44.
44.
Fourty three.
43?
All gone. I need to get more.
Friday, you understand Friday?
Friday... here, all right?
All right, thank you.
Okay.
I have.
You have.
She... he... has.
We...
Have.
Friend.
Good?
Yes.
All, all of them. Inside, all of them in the..
Did you give him the trousers?
What?
None of those trousers will fit us.
Four of us could fit into one pair!
In one!
Stop!
Stop, stop.
For fuck's sake, stop. You dickhead.
You dickhead.
Relax, arsehole.
Aren't you doing Ramadan?
Sure, I'm doing Ramadan.
Get out of here,
you're a pain in my arse.
Get away from him.
Listen, take them away.
Look, look...
Close the door, did you bring the filter?
Bring me the pen.
Give me a couple of drops of shampoo.
Shake it a bit.
Enough.
Give me a little drop.
A tiny bit.
Enough.
What do you want to get done?
H
Okay.
J, the first letter of my mum's name,
also a heart,
and also F L, and that's it.
Do you want a big heart?
No. Only a little one.
Do this, and next to it the H.
Jadija?
You're getting Jadija,
be patient and I'll sort you out.
I want H and A.
All done, I'll sort you out, friend.
You know what you're going to do now? Sleep.
Like this?
Like this, with your head here.
It's my skin...
tuc, tuc, tuc, tuc...
I can't do tuc, tuc, tuc... brother.
Hold on a little.
Keep going...
You're entering Hell.
And you?
I'm crazy!
Is there anyone before me?
Who else hasn't signed up?
You?
Colour. No. Cut?
Nothing.
Okay. Great.
Look friend, she's going to do the white dye.
Do you want what I'm getting?
I want it all white.
When I got here, I had really short hair.
How long have you had dreads for?
Three months.
You... you, how long?
You, how long?
She's asking how long you've had dreads for.
Years, years.
Four, four. Four years.
Four years.
Boys, I'm going to tell you something.
No one is going to steal anything.
If anyone steals anything, I'll fucking lose it.
This is cool, Patri.
Look, this is the one I told you about.
Patri, look.
Yeah...good.
And now... this.
Alright.
A question!
For me?
Yesterday... before.. I heard about you.
That you were boy, or girl...
Chique?
Chique.
Girl, boy, chique.
You?
Yes.
Mix, mix.
Mix? DETR
A bit girl, a bit boy.
So, how do you feel?
Good!
What does it say in your passport?
Girl.
A little bit of machine.
No charge.
A little bit.
No, no, zero charge.
Patri, the hair, boy
But the body, girl.
More or less, more or less, more or less.
Cause I don't dress like a girl.
You understand?
res.
Yeah? Okay.
So my aesthetic, mix.
No boy, no girl.
- No problem, no problem.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Girl!
Girl? Not girl.
Her, not girl.
Not girl.
What's up, not girl?
I'm not girl.
Not girl?
Yes.
No.
I'm a boy.
You're a girl.
No.
I'm chique.
Chique.
Not girl, not boy..
Girl... boy... Chique!
Impossible.
Not impossible, because I'm here and I exist.
See you later! Impossible.
No, but explain to me, what's this?
What's going on?
I'm not a girl, not a boy.
I don't want to be a girl, don't want to be a boy.
I'm in the middle.
Only you?
I'm in the middle. Chique.
Good.
Black people are the same, not a problem.
Good, and you?
Patri...
Thank you!
Looking good, looking good!
Minor: seventeen years old.
Presents with anxiety.
ANI
RISE AND
USE AND SHIN
Give me a bit.
He's scared.
He's scared of the police.
Really?
The police recognised him.
But this was in the afternoon?
We called the lady that takes us in the car.
The man took us in the car.
We're very tired here.
We don't eat well.
Since we're here, ACCEM has done nothing for us.
People come to give us clothes,
it's difficult for us.
If you look, you'll see we have lots of problems.
We want them to help us go to mainland Spain,
or even go to Senegal to reunite with our families.
Someone do something so we can get out of here.
We're very, very, very tired.
Listen; Lucky Dube.
No one knows what happened.
People betrayed him.
Cold.
Today it's really cold.
can hear him clearly... he whispers in the air,
His voice came... loud...
asked for, was a prayer...
Silvia!
Hello, how are you?
Good, all fine?
Yes, I am good.
Nice to meet you.
I was waiting for you.
Mimi sent me some food for you.
Yeah, yeah, thanks.
I hope it's enough.
Thank you.
What's happening, how are you doing?
I'm good,
I try to stay here, to find a solution to go from here.
It must be so difficult to be there.
In these conditions everything is difficult,
to travel, to do anything.
So, no solution... only, waiting.
I can't imagine how it is to live there.
Yeah, it's very difficult.
So sorry, for you. I'm so sorry
lo, this is not about you, this is you know, my decision, m
life,
and also, this is the decision of the government.
Yeah, I know, it's about European politics.
Yeah, to open the airport to all these people,
o travel, because all these people don't want to stay her
they don't come to Tenerife or other islands,
everyone wants to travel, maybe France, Spain, other
everyone here has the same dream.
But, in these conditions, the situation is very, very bad.
It's tough, living in conditions like this.
Because there's lots of different nationalities, you know
nere's Moroccans, Senegalese, Ghambian... other countri
Lots of people, different mentalities, languages, cultures
We have a lot of time, a lot of free time,
but we don't do anything with this time.
We're tired of thinking, what will they do with us?
All the time thinking, thinking, thinking, you know?
This is the situation here.
What's your name?
My name is...
No no. You ask.
What's your name?
My name is Hassanka.
My name's Mohammed.
What's your name?
My name is Vilall.
What name?
No, no, no. What's your name?
What's your name? With your.
It's really near to the Canaries, real near.
Near.
Far... you remember? Far away...
and near.
Near, yes.
It's near.
You know what you're doing, right?
Were you in college, or what?
Cut from here, upwards
Give me a fade, and leave my beard. Just cut a little
Lumme
Lumme?
umm
-umme
Lumme?
Lumme
Of course Lumme, course, course.
Anything else?
White or black?
White.
Here, a name here.
One?
Name here?
Colour, Modou Fah.
Modou Fah, yes, here.
Modou.
Modou, yes?
I'm, what person?
Friend, you're four.
- Me?
You're four.
Four.
Four. No problem, four.
This man's going to get caught in the airport and deportes
To eat olives.
Faiezel, finish up and get the next one.
Buddy, get me a good machine to cut quickly.
Here, here, swap with me.
I'm fourth, but I should be first. Up.
If you don't like it, I can put you first.
No, it's not a problem.
If you want, I can rub it out.
They'll confuse me with someone else.
What's your name, mate?
I want to dye it black but there's others before me.
You're free. Do what you like.
I came before, and there was someone first. I don't know
who.
Hey, Suada...
go see what they're doing, I can see the're haning around
there.
Just Moroccans cutting their har today. Morocco only.
Okay, you were here yesterday, but it was busy.
Okay? Every day a new day.
You're a friend, no problem. Now, you to me, now
I'll come back tomorrow, and your hair will already be cut
You have machines here.
You always get your hair cut.
Why do you want to cut your hair today?
No, no, no..
Yes, yes, thanks, thanks, thanks.
yes, hanks thanks
Thanks for helping. The end.
Good people, no zig zag
Mohamed, I didn't expect that from you,
she's good, and different.
She's not going to play you.
She's different, poor thing.
Everyone here is fucked.
meone working here won't waste their time with the gan
here
Two for one?
No problem, whatever you say.
One, one is fine.
No problem.
Morocco is pretty good!
Problems, Morocco.
No zig zag, no zig zag.
No zig zag.
It's all done.
Be calm, be calm.
In Spanish; it's all good.
Morocco and Spain... sisters.
Sisters.
No problem.
Work... good money... no zig zag..
...work.
The camp is very cold.
Cold. Very, very, very..
Cold.
Yesterday, I didn't sleep.
Always...
I don't smoke... no tobacco, nothing.
Nothing, nothing, nothing..
Friend, friend, friend, friend..
Hello mama... a bracelet?
Hello, girls.
A bracelet, please?
Dad?
Hello, a bracelet, please?
A bracelet, please?
Hello.
Girl.
I'm sorry, take one.
Friends, a bracelet. please.
Hello. Take one.
Give me dates.
Calm yourself.
How many times have I given you already?
Come on, go. Leave that!
Dates, dates.
Give me dates.
I said no!
Calm down.
Come on, come on.
Every day I'll bring some,
now we all need to do a blessing.
A blessing to God.
To all who have problems here, may God help them.
May God bless us.
May God help those who want to go to the mainland.
To the volunteers who bring us things,
may God bless them.
Let us pray to Sallatu Fatiha.
We ask for blessings for all.
Amen, Amen. Thank you, thank you.
May God help us.
Ah, I think there's two t-shirts here.
I don't know if the boys from next door's camp
took it over yesterday, or when.
They day before yesterday, and yesterday
they took them all to do a PCR test.
We've been here for a long time, really.
We'll protest today, too.
If we were ill they'd already have sent us to Madrid.
We wouldn't be here.
My God, we still have such a way to go.
We came to Europe to change our lives,
we've been here three months,
and we don't even have a passport.
No passport, no ID, no money to eat or smoke.
I don't know what we'll do.
No food, no good. Lots of people in the showers.
If you want your tooth out... AccEM, please, my tooth.
And they say, tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow. No, when? What do you want tomorrow?
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
ACCEM says, tomorrow..
and we sleep. We must be grateful.
It's cause there's lots of people.
And only one doctor?
How many are there?
Nearly 1,600.
Nearly 1,600, friend.
If there's 1,600, what will they do with them?
Yes, 1,600. They all want to come to Spain.
And they all want their papers, to go to the doctor,
go to the police to claim asylum.
Yes, asylum. They do it.
Were you in the hotel too?
I was in a five star one.
Where did you come in?
In a five star one?
We didn't know we'd be fucked in Spain.
You know about that, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Who was to know this would happen?
To eat or drink. Food and drink.
I'm a student...
We were together and kept each other company,
You were with me, we never thought of being apart,
I gave you my heart and I fell in love,
With a broken heart, I look at life,
Turn around, tell me we've won
Losing your love killed me, you are hurting too,
I'm wounded and my heart is broken.
The wave took me, the wave took me,
Left me with a heart full ot pain
I'd like to see my fate.
And my mother I left crying,
It took me, the longing took me,
and left me with a saddened heart,
And my mother I left crying,
Look at what happened,
the understanding between us,
But the system changed
and I suffer the separation,
Because you hurried away and left my heart alone.
You put me in a boat that took me,
but my mothers' voice made me weep.
The waves exhaust us, all the problems
exhaust us, they close the doors we knock on.
I miss you mum, I'm hoping to hold you soon,
I want us to live together, may God help us.
This faraway house,
My sadness and problems continue,
You have to live through it.
deRechoshum We bece
deRechoshumanes
6AdoNefueRONLOS We arrived Rece ived
deRechoshumanes Rece ived us asref
And We bece
deRechoshumanes And We bece
Please, we only have one goal.
That they let us travel.
Have we given our life to death to find misery here?
Why?
Most of the people who got on the dinghies with us,
are dead.
Dead!
They're dead.
Have we given our life to death to find misery here?
Why?
I prefer to have.
You know what? Give me a solution.
Open the door so I can go to Morocco or Spain.
Either here, or there.
Because I'm not staying here.
You know what it is? It's racism.
Racism, discrimination.
Here, we don't live in a camp.
It's not a camp, it's not a centre,
It's a prison.
It's a prison!
Here! Here!
Whilst we're sleeping,
the police come in and beat us. Why?
We're not criminals, we're not drug addicts.
We're here for our families; to work,
for our future.
I'll help, you look after it, okay?
Okay? Yes?
Good.
Inside here, there's an infection.
Okay?
We're going to treat it, okay?
Good.
We'll lift it, clean,
clean, and then cover it.
Pain?
A little pain.
That's fine.
Are you strong?
Yes.
Good, my friend, good.
Said told me to write him a note,
because he needs a psychiatrist,
because he says that...
he wants to take pills to take his life,
because he thinks the NGO is mocking him.
And he's going to the doctor to show him the note.
They're desperate.
There's no solutions,
no one cares for them,
they don't have a good diet,
there's no hygiene.
I think that, most of the psychological problems,
would be greatly reduced by
with more free time activities, right?
Get them out of their routine, their own heads,
all the tragedy,
all the time they have to kill.
Don't take it off. It's not too bad, okay?
Don't take it off, no.
Keep it on,
but be very careful.
No water,
no earth,
no dirt.
Okay? Look after it well
Okay?
Paracetamol?
es.
I'll see what pain you have first.
Socks, shoe,
and you're good,
with your shoes on.
No one is here to steal;
obviously if we all get out,
there'll always be someone that will, we know.
But we're locked up here against our will,
and the're not respecting our rights.
Except if you go mad and self-harm,
who knows what happens to them.
God forgive them, I don't envy them.
To each his own luck.
But their obligation is to find us a solution.
If you see the Moroccans now, they're calm,
but if you take them to the limit, they may explode.
In a bad way.
If the people of Spain and their government,
have a problem with Morocco, let them sort it out.
Don't say that, don't talk like that.
Speak for yourself, speak for yourself.
Let him continue, calm down!
Let him speak.
Mind your own business.
If this is Spanish politics,
of the Spanish government,
if it has some conflict with Morocco,
let it stay between them.
We are people,
we don't win with Morocco or Spain.
The African riches were taken by France, Spain, Morocco
And we have nothing,
and these people, these youth,
each doing something,
some work with their hands, and all have a job.
I want these words to reach you,
if Spanish politicians won't do anything,
don't let the immigrants suffer.
Even the Canarian people are of migrant origin.
The origins of the Canaries, are migrants.
The Berber.
We have nothing to do with politics of either side.
But, I insist, Canary people were also migrants.
It's someone with phsychological problems.
Yes, yes.
But it's normal.
You go tell him it's not worth it,
explain to him that his life is worth more!
It's fine, it's the protocol.
It's fine,
don't worry.
I suffered in Morocco!
So I came here! I have no parents,
I want to end this suffering!
Ihave no parents, no siblings.
I have no parents to feed me.
They took them to Madrid, but not me, why!
Get away, get away. Turn back.
Security's turning back.
Pain? Good, good, it's okay, okay?
Pain?
No.
It's clean now, hey?
It's bleeding well.
Pain?
No.
Difficult to heal.
Every day.
Every day, you look after it, okay?
No.
With the infirmary, good.
With friends...
not good.
When? One day, two days, three..
Four.
Four days?
Yes.
And, with what?
Say I went to separate people and they hit me with a rocl
He wasn't fighting.
He separated them,
and they hit him with a rock.
Friends were fighting and he separated them.
Tell her, tell her... explain it to her.
Was it with this, or this?
She's asking whether it was a fist or a rock.
Rock, rock.
Hashdra means rock?
Throw that in the bin.
Tomorrow she's coming to change it.
Tomorrow, tomorrow.
You..
You...
clean, shower.
Yeah?
The shower at ACCEM is cold. Cold shower.
No water.
You need to help your friend, here.
Tomorrow, I...
No water...
here.
Tomorrow, I'll be here.
And I'll ask. Is your friend helping?
And he'll tell me.
Very good.
Tomorrow, more.
Wash, alcohol. Wash, hands.
Wash, hands. Wash.
How are you?
All right?
All right, all right.
tent later, okay?
After? Are you coming?
No, you come to the A, okay?
You coming to the tent?
Ibrahim?
What tent is it, Ibrahim?
Tent 8
number eight
in
Tent three or tent eight?
Two
Sector two
Sector three, tent two
Okay, I'll go after
Yay! Finally!
No, not the moustache.
The moustache.
No, no, no
My moustache! No, no!
Like this?
There's lots I don't understand and they,
help me manage or understand what's happening.
So yes, I guess this is a space for
mediation between.
Senegalese and Moroccans, which is
where most problems are.
Which is what I tell them,
the problem isn't whether
they're from Senegal or Morocco
It's that they're hungry, tired, desperate,
they don't want to be here, they want to wor
If lockdown messed with our heads,
and has spawned a load of psychological problems,
imagine being here day and night..
without being able to do anything or communicate,
with people here, cause there's
a massive language barrier.
The weird thing is that they've
not already burnt this to the ground.
If they did this to the majority of us, well...
Is this journalist going to be here all the time?
Don't worry, he's fine where he is.
Gaba, come get your hair cut.
Oh, you're finished?
You'll see on Youtube, we'll be
shown as dangerous.
I heard someone say once,
geographically our body is in Africa
our heart is in America,
and our mind is in Europe.
And it's what works the worst.
There's also a really nice poem that says
The more we think we're from the North
the dust storms always come to remind us who we are.
o me this is like a great big dust storm
Hello?
Hello, how are you?
Good!
I'm okay, how are you all?
Good, good..
Are you all right?
Thank God for giving me life to listen to you.
God bless you. Are you all right?
I miss you so much.
I miss you all lots too. Put me onto Mahir.
It's my father, it's my father!
It's daddy, it's daddy, Good my love, yes my son.
I miss you, my heart.
They said you're misbehaving Mahir...
No, no.
I heard Mahir is misbehaving. But I don't know..
I just can't get outside very much.
Oh, yeah?
How was your birthday? Did mum make you
a. birthday cake, or something else?
I got presents!
Yeah?
Tell me who's looking after you..
Mummy is looking after me, and Hassana.
Hassana, your uncle Karim,
my dad, auntie Fatima.
Tell me, school... are you studying hard?
Yes! I got a nine!
Nine!
God is great.
Here.
talk.
Thank God. My son has grown up.
Listen to dad, Mahir.
Right now in in this place,
God willing soon I'll be able to work,
people here will help me
You understand, son?
God willing I'll get the papers, go get you,
and I'll take care of you son.
I'll bring you with me to Spain, France
or wherever you want. God willing
Daddy, I'm cross with you.
You're cross with me?
But, why?
I'm cross with you.
What have I done to you?
But, what have I done to you son?
Come now. I'm cross. I want you to come back now.
My country...
Who will help me to return to my country?
Immigration isn't easy.
Mum and dad wait for me, behind me.
Who will help me to return to my country?
It's so cold.
Dude, dude, look at that plane!
I hope very soon we can do something like that.
Fuck, for God's sake man.
God willing.